[{"product_id":1,"licence_name":"Harry Potter","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Luna","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Harry Potter","product_price":1940.92,"dues":4,"product_sku":"HPT001001","img_front":"/img/harry-potter/luna-1.webp","img_back":"/img/harry-potter/luna-box.webp"},{"product_id":2,"licence_name":"Harry Potter","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Hermione","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Harry Potter","product_price":1609.45,"dues":5,"product_sku":"HPT001002","img_front":"/img/harry-potter/hermione-1.webp","img_back":"/img/harry-potter/hermione-box.webp"},{"product_id":3,"licence_name":"Star Wars","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Baby Yoda","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars","product_price":1733.5,"dues":9,"product_sku":"STW001003","img_front":"/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-1.webp","img_back":"/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-box.webp"},{"product_id":4,"licence_name":"Star Wars","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Trooper","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars","product_price":1874.35,"dues":3,"product_sku":"STW001004","img_front":"/img/star-wars/trooper-1.webp","img_back":"/img/star-wars/trooper-box.webp"},{"product_id":5,"licence_name":"Star Wars","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Bobba Feth","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars","product_price":1804.74,"dues":10,"product_sku":"STW001005","img_front":"/img/star-wars/bobbafeth-1.webp","img_back":"/img/star-wars/bobbafeth-box.webp"},{"product_id":6,"licence_name":"Star Wars","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Baby Yoda","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars","product_price":1847.62,"dues":5,"product_sku":"STW001006","img_front":"/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-1.webp","img_back":"/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-box.webp"},{"product_id":7,"licence_name":"Star Wars","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Luke","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars","product_price":1837.9,"dues":4,"product_sku":"STW001007","img_front":"/img/star-wars/luke-1.webp","img_back":"/img/star-wars/luke-box.webp"},{"product_id":8,"licence_name":"Star Wars","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Trooper","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars","product_price":1854.48,"dues":0,"product_sku":"STW001008","img_front":"/img/star-wars/trooper-1.webp","img_back":"/img/star-wars/trooper-box.webp"},{"product_id":9,"licence_name":"Star Wars","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Trooper","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars","product_price":1787,"dues":4,"product_sku":"STW001009","img_front":"/img/star-wars/trooper-1.webp","img_back":"/img/star-wars/trooper-box.webp"},{"product_id":10,"licence_name":"Pokemon","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Vulpix","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon","product_price":1849.24,"dues":4,"product_sku":"PKM001010","img_front":"/img/pokemon/vulpix-1.webp","img_back":"/img/pokemon/vulpix-box.webp"},{"product_id":11,"licence_name":"Pokemon","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Charmander","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon","product_price":1750.35,"dues":8,"product_sku":"PKM001011","img_front":"/img/pokemon/charmander-1.webp","img_back":"/img/pokemon/charmander-box.webp"},{"product_id":12,"licence_name":"Star Wars","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Baby Yoda","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars","product_price":2105.22,"dues":11,"product_sku":"STW001012","img_front":"/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-1.webp","img_back":"/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-box.webp"},{"product_id":13,"licence_name":"Harry Potter","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Snape Patronus","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Harry Potter","product_price":1740.55,"dues":3,"product_sku":"HPT001013","img_front":"/img/harry-potter/snape-patronus-1.webp","img_back":"/img/harry-potter/snape-patronus-box.webp"},{"product_id":14,"licence_name":"Pokemon","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Vulpix","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon","product_price":1797.74,"dues":10,"product_sku":"PKM001014","img_front":"/img/pokemon/vulpix-1.webp","img_back":"/img/pokemon/vulpix-box.webp"},{"product_id":15,"licence_name":"Harry Potter","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Luna","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Harry Potter","product_price":1853.38,"dues":7,"product_sku":"HPT001015","img_front":"/img/harry-potter/luna-1.webp","img_back":"/img/harry-potter/luna-box.webp"},{"product_id":16,"licence_name":"Pokemon","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Charmander","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon","product_price":1660.12,"dues":9,"product_sku":"PKM001016","img_front":"/img/pokemon/charmander-1.webp","img_back":"/img/pokemon/charmander-box.webp"},{"product_id":17,"licence_name":"Star Wars","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Luke","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars","product_price":1654.72,"dues":5,"product_sku":"STW001017","img_front":"/img/star-wars/luke-1.webp","img_back":"/img/star-wars/luke-box.webp"},{"product_id":18,"licence_name":"Star Wars","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Baby Yoda","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Star Wars","product_price":1835.62,"dues":4,"product_sku":"STW001018","img_front":"/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-1.webp","img_back":"/img/star-wars/baby-yoda-box.webp"},{"product_id":19,"licence_name":"Pokemon","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Dragonite","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon","product_price":1863.88,"dues":7,"product_sku":"PKM001019","img_front":"/img/pokemon/dragonite-1.webp","img_back":"/img/pokemon/dragonite-box.webp"},{"product_id":20,"licence_name":"Pokemon","category_name":"Figuras coleccionables","product_name":"Dragonite","product_description":"Figura coleccionable Pokemon","product_price":1625.09,"dues":7,"product_sku":"PKM001020","img_front":"/img/pokemon/dragonite-1.webp","img_back":"/img/pokemon/dragonite-box.webp"}]